One of is muscle sparing.
This idea that you could do
a shoulder replacement or a
joint replacement and you
wouldn't have
to cut the muscles.
Subscapularis.
For example, the
subscapularis.
So the subscap's in the
front of your shoulder,
The subscap, if you cut into
it, needs to heal,
like any other muscle you
do,
and that's a restriction for
six weeks,
and it sometimes can lead to
lifelong problems, right?
So imagine if I did a
shoulder replacement
without cutting that muscle
ever.
First of all, you have no
restrictions to start,
you get back to work, you
have no limitations,
and then you can get back to
doing things
and you don't have that risk
of it failing down the
road.
So the fact that we've even
developed techniques
to be able to do so like
that,